http://www.stlzoo.org/privacypolicy

The Zoo is NOW OPEN. Reservations are required to visit. Review the Zoo’s reopening guidelines and make a reservation.
Donate Online
Saint Louis Zoo
AboutMissionHistoryOrganizationOur BoardsEmploymentBlogWhy Zoos MatterZoo-Museum DistrictFinancialsEconomic ImpactContact UsVisitZoo ReservationsAnimalsAbout the AnimalsVeterinary HospitalAnimal Food & Nutrition CenterReproductive & Behavioral SciencesEnrichment & TrainingSpecies Survival PlansSo You Want to be a Zookeeper?ConservationSaint Louis Zoo WildCare InstituteSaint Louis Zoo Institute for Conservation MedicineWe Conserve ResourcesDo-It-Yourself Conservation#byetobagsEducationVirtual Conservation LearningPreschoolIndividuals & FamiliesScouts and Youth GroupsSchool GroupsTeachersHomework HelperZoo DocentsZoo ALIVE Teen VolunteersFrogWatch USAEventsCalendar of EventsRent the ZooMembershipCOVID-19 and Your Zoo MembershipGift MembershipsZoo Young ProfessionalsFrequently Asked QuestionsMarlin Perkins SocietySaint Louis Zoo Matching Gift CompaniesHoliday Gift MembershipGiveCritical Animal Care FundZoo Parents ProgramVolunteerPlanned GivingTributes & Commemorative BricksCorporate PartnersZoo MerchandiseZoo License Plate
Search
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Overall Policy
Thank you for visiting our web site. We're pleased to share our policy regarding the use of information received here. Privacy is of great concern to the Saint Louis Zoo. We are committed to protecting your privacy and the security of the information that you may provide to us.
Personal Information
We do not track individual users. Your e-mail address or other personal information is not collected unless you sign up for an e-newsletter or provide it on a form or survey. The Saint Louis Zoo will never sell your e-mail address or share it with anyone else not directly affiliated with the Saint Louis Zoo. We will comply with legitimate government or legal requests as necessary to protect our organization or comply with laws.
You must be age 13 or older to receive emails from the Saint Louis Zoo.
Membership
The Zoo never sells our member lists to telemarketing or direct mail firms. However, from time to time we do exchange the names of our members with other cultural institutions in the St. Louis area. If you do not wish your name to be included in those exchanges, please e-mail membership@stlzoo.org.
Traffic Analysis
We do analyze traffic to this site. We collect statistical data on an aggregated basis, through a "Log Analysis" program of site statistics. For example, we collect data such as the domain names of servers that bring visitors to our site and the search terms that were used to help visitors find our site, and we count the number of visitors and keep track of where they go on our site. Such information allows us to find out what areas users visit most frequently and what services they access the most, which enables us to create a better overall experience for our users.
Cookies
To gather traffic analysis data as referenced above, we use "cookie" technology which collects data in aggregate form, not by individual user. Browser cookies are small data files stored by your browser that differentiate users and maintain data related to users during navigation. The cookies placed by our server do not gather personal information about you, do not provide any way for us to contact you, and do not get information about your computer; they simply allow us to enhance our site by letting us know what sections are visited most frequently. The use of cookies is common on the Internet and our use of them is similar to that of other reputable online organizations.
Links To Other Sites
Our site contains links to other sites and Internet resources. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites and Internet resources.
Updates to Privacy Policy
We may update these privacy policies periodically, and we encourage visitors to review them on a regular basis.
Questions & Concerns
Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to privacy@stlzoo.org.
WebSanity Top Secret
